
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Javascript is an _______ language?",
    answer: "Object Oriented",
    options: [
      "Object-Based",
      "Object Oriented",
      "Procedural",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following keywords is used to define a variable in Javascript?",
    answer: "Both A and B",
    options: [
      "var",
      "let",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following methods is used to access HTML elements using Javascript??",
    answer: "Both A and B",
    options: [
      "getElementById()",
      "getElementByClassName()",
      "Both A and B",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Upon encountering empty statements, what does the Javascript Interpreter do?",
    answer: "Ignores the statement",
    options: [
      "Ignores the statement",
      "Throws an error",
      "Executes the statement",
      "Gives a warning"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following methods can be used to display data in some form using Javascript?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "document.write()",
      "console.log()",
      "window.alert()",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
  numb: 6,
  question: "How can a datatype be declared to be a constant type?",
  answer: "const",
  options: [
    "const",
    "let",
    "var",
    "constant"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "When the switch statement matches the expression with the given labels, how is the comparison done?",
  answer: "Both the datatype and the result of the expression are compared", 
  options: [
    "Both the datatype and the result of the expression are compared",
    "Only the datatype of the expression is compared",
    "Only the value of the expression is compared",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "When an operator’s value is NULL, the typeof returned by the unary operator is:",
  answer: "Object",
  options: [
  "Object",
  "Boolean",
  "Integer",
  "Undefined",
]
}, 
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "What does the Javascript “debugger” statement do?",
  answer: "It acts as a breakpoint in a program",
  options: [
  "It acts as a breakpoint in a program",
  "It stops the execution of a program",
  "It will debug all the error in the program at runtime",
  "All of the above"
]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "Which of the following are closures in Javascript?",
  answer: "All of the above",
  options: [
  "All of the above",
  "Vaiables",
  "Functions",
  "Objects"
]
},
]